<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>1trickPwnyta's Ideology Patch</name>
	<author>1trickPwnyta</author>
	<packageId>ideologypatch.1trickPwnyta</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
This mod makes a handful of small tweaks to the Ideology DLC that are intended to make the game a bit more enjoyable without changing the gameplay too much.

Full list of tweaks:
- Ranchers no longer get upset about planting "human food crops". They already get a mood penalty for eating vegetables; they don't need another one just for planting them. Besides, who says you're planting them in order to eat them? Maybe you just want to make chemfuel. Or you want to have food onhand that you can use to train your animals.
- Dryads no longer wander further from their tree than the building radius warning (12 tiles -> 7.9 tiles). This makes it more intuitive to build a wall around the tree just outside the warning radius to keep the dryads safe from raiders.
- When you receive a letter for finishing converting a prisoner, the Jump to location link selects the prisoner that was converted rather than the person who did the converting. This makes it easier to select a new prisoner interaction such as Recruit.
- Starting research that unlocks things that "require memes that none of your people believe" no longer triggers a pop-up unless ALL of the unlocked things require such memes. In other words, you won't be bothered if there's anything that you CAN build.
- When beginning a role change ritual, the role selected by default will be an unfilled role unless all roles are filled so you don't accidentally assign the moral guide role twice and make someone unhappy, for example.
- Sets the default female clothing requirement for ideologies to groin covering only, as it is for men.
- Sets the default physical love precept to free so that people can have premarital sex like they did before Ideology.
- Disables the darkness mood debuff for the Tunneler meme (specifically the Fungus: Preferred precept, because if you like fungus you shouldn't hate planting it).
- Adds the Corpses: Don't Care precept to the Bloodfeeding meme (because cannibalism).
- Changes the nudity precept "Pants at most" to "Pants only", which does the same thing but is worded correctly.
- Pawns with an ideology that prohibit recreational drugs will no longer randomly use recreational drugs unless they have a chemical need trait.
- Gauranlen tree-connected pawns will no longer ignore their needs for hours at a time while pruning the tree. It's not like the tree is the golden cube.
- Newly built lights default to darklight setting if the player's primary ideology prefers darklight.
- Shows a message when an ideology ritual comes off cooldown so you don't forget to perform it again.
- Brings back the "Look change desired" mechanic that mysteriously disappears with Biotech enabled.

=== Updates ===
08/02/2024: Remove patch from 1.4 version
06/25/2024: Use darklight by default in darkness ideologies
06/11/2024: Add settings to toggle each tweak
05/24/2024: Remove artificial enhancement calculation change. Genies were not bugged after all.
04/29/2024: Prevent pawns from pruning the tree non-stop while ignoring their own needs
04/09/2024: Stopped pawns against recreational drug use from using recreational drugs
03/20/2024: Update to 1.5
08/28/2023: Fixed prosthetics count bug
08/18/2023: Renamed Pants at most to Pants only
08/17/2023: Disabled the darkness thought for fungus: preferred, associate corpses: don't care with bloodfeeding meme
10/26/2022: Removed debugging messages from the dev log
10/26/2022: Added the default physical love precept

=== Credits ===
Mod icon: twitter.com/mouse_draws
	</description>
	<url>https://github.com/1trickPwnyta/IdeologyPatch</url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
